音质。你知道那种感觉吧：隔着拥挤的房间听到一个声音，就能
Voice quality. You know how you hear a voice across a crowded room and you can
判断它是美国口音。这里起作用的是什么？要回答这个问题，我们先
just tell that it's American? What's at play there? To answer that question, let's
定义一下术语。美式发音里的音质是什么？它是
first define our terms. What is voice quality in the American sound? It's a
发声位置和节奏的结合，也就是喉部音色加上
combination of vocal placement and cadence. This means a throaty sound and a
阶梯式语调。听英国喜剧演员 Eddie Izzard 模仿美式
stair-step intonation. Listen to British comedian Eddie Izzard imitate the American
口音：肯尼迪总统成了美国总统。
accent. President Kennedy became the president of the United States of America.
他去了柏林，说：“柏林的人民，柏林的人民。”我不会模仿
And he went to Berlin. And he said, people of Berlin, people of Berlin. I can't do an
肯尼迪总统，所以他们说：“柏林人民。”注意他模仿美式
impression of President Kennedy, so they said, people of Berlin. Notice how his
口音时，声音怎样往喉咙后部移动，并向胸腔下沉。
voice moves back in his throat and down in his chest when he's imitating the American
这种喉部音色是一个关键特征。甚至还有一个
accent. This throaty quality is an essential characteristic. There's even a
专门的词来描述它：rhoticity，也就是 hard、far 里的那个扎实 R 音。
fancy word to describe it, rhoticity, which is that solid R as in hard and far. There
有些地区方言明显缺少 rhoticity，比如经典的
are regional dialects that are notable for lacking rhoticity, such as the classic
比如经典的波士顿口音：“把车停在哈佛园里”，但
Bostonian, pack your car and have a yard for park your car in Harvard Yard, but the
但绝大多数美国人都会把 R 发得很明显。语调、音质
overwhelming majority of Americans growl out the R. Intonation, voice quality, and
和分句都会共同形成独特的美式声音，此外还包括一种随意的
phrasing all contribute to the uniquely American voice, along with a casual
这种放松的态度，使美国英语不同于
relaxed attitude. This relaxation causes American English to differ from the
英式英语更清脆的发音。在音质方面，你会调整自己的声音。
crisper sounds of British English. Within voice quality, you'll be adjusting your
音量：稍微更响，还是压低、轻声；音高：高音还是
volume, a little louder versus muted or murmured, pitch, high-pitched versus a
更低的声区；气流：爆破、嘶擦或嗡鸣；以及声音从哪里
deeper register, airflow, popped, hissed, or buzzed, and where the voice is
发出：喉咙和胸腔，还是头部和鼻腔。美国人通常会稍微
generated, throat and chest versus head and nose. Americans tend to be a little
比你习惯的更响亮。刻板印象中的美国人声音更大，
louder than you're accustomed to. The stereotypical American is louder, a little
更直接、更热闹，一见面就友好，非正式，还带点玩笑感。
brasher, more boisterous, immediately friendly, informal, and slightly jokey.
重要的是，要比平常更用力地把声音投射出去。
It's important to project your voice out with more force than usual, and you'll
需要更多气息才能把它推出去。小孩声音很大，对吧？
need more breath to push it out. Kids are loud, right? Things stick in their heads
因为他们会大声喊出来。现在也大声喊出来！在家里、车里或其他私密空间，
because they yell them out. Yell this out! In the privacy of your home, car, or
甚至在山顶上，把这些音和练习句大声喊出来，
mountaintop, get out and yell some of these sounds and practice sentences so
让它真正进入你的脑子里。不要害怕夸张练习。
that you can get it really in your head. Don't be afraid to exaggerate and go way
比你以为的美式口音还要夸张。
further than you think the American accent actually is. This will help you embrace
这种声音。
the sound.